This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum-gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
After overcoming a trap set by the Navy,
he flies toward the scaffold, his goal in sight.
The White Beard Pirates soon joined Luffy,
using a paddle boat that was hidden at the bottom of the bay,
to break into the plaza where the battle rages on.
Now for second gear!
The White Beard Pirates soon joined Luffy's brother Ace.
Huh, you almost made it.
Everyone, swim across the bay towards oars!
Sir, we have a problem!
Another coated pirate ship's about to enter the bay,
and it's coming fast!
Now sink that thing!
Drop it like the Moby Dick!
Seize fire!
The ship is too fast!
Aim your firing oars!
That's insane!
He plucked the ship right out of the bay!
This is bad!
They've broken through the encircling walls!
That's enough!
My sons, please, stay back.
Listen up, Pirates!
Bring Ace to safety!
And once you're done with that,
destroy the Navy!
Hooray!
Are you with me?
Yeah.
I fear we can't hold back anymore.
This battle may be our last.
Luffy at the end of his tether!
An all-out battle at the Ori's plaza!
The show's over, fratty poor sap who possesses devil fruit powers and falls into the sea!
How tragic to end like this!
Or not!
Another glorious maneuver to escape certain death!
What are you doing, Ivankov?
Now then, I wonder, what's going on?
I cannot believe he just shushed me!
While I'm here, just trying to stay afloat, the real struggles happening on the other side.
Oh no, please tell me you're not already.
Boiled alive, burnt to a crisp, a frozen solid!
Poor boy!
They're killing you!
Stop that!
We need to hurry!
Hey!
This entire mess is all your fault!
It is?
How so?
Don't play dumb!
You're a warlord, or ex-warlord!
You're supposed to defeat the Navy and rescue Ace Boy!
I don't think that's possible.
Mess of up good, boys!
Oars.
Thanks, pal.
Clear a path for me.
And be quick.
Watch out, you guys!
He's gearing up!
Sure you want to do that?
Ace Ball!
Whitebeard's a Popsicle!
We got him!
Oh no!
We broke out.
Those vibrations can't be frozen.
Tough luck.
Ice!
Admiral Kuzan!
He's been stabbed!
Kuzo-ki-ji dead!
No!
Doing fine, thank you.
Go, Ice Block!
Partison!
Go!
I'll fight!
I'm counting!
I'm counting on you, son!
Had him!
Damn!
Don't stop moving!
We're almost there!
Ah!
The scaffold is straight ahead, but first we need to break through these cracks!
Stop moving! We're almost there!
Hurry up and die!
You and the rest of the filthy pirate scum!
Almost!
The encircling walls went up. How come? Why haven't they surrendered yet?
Damn it! Whitebeard and Straw Hat are almost to the scaffold!
When that time comes, I'll be even stronger! Strong enough to capture you!
Because I promised myself that I'll keep trying…
Till…
Till I become a Marine Admiral!
I made us both that promise, but I still haven't improved a bit!
Luffy!
I've got to fight!
Straw Hat Luffy!
I, Momonga, am the Navy Vice Admiral who will cut you down!
It ends here.
The same rank as Grandpa!
Shave?
Moon Wolf!
Oh…
If I said we're all the same rank as Grandpa…
Shave?
Moon Wolf!
Second gear!
You're finished, Straw Hat! Finger Pistol!
Dumb kid. Reckless. He's too green.
But...one thing is certain. He never gives up.
Garp, don't you dare forget whose side you're on.
You're full of courage, aren't you?
But take this word of advice, if you're simply not strong enough,
no matter how courageous you may be, you won't even come close to saving him.
He...he just can't compete with the Admirals.
No way. Luffy, get up!
Kill Whitebeard! Keep pushing him back!
Why don't you just give up?
No!
Stop!
You're not the only adventures!
No!
Nice.
Huh, well, seems the White Beard brand
is losing some of its punch.
Surely you could have done better
than let that youngster lead the attack.
I mean, look at him.
The boy is hardly breathing.
Guess that's partially my fault.
Sad pops! Let's block the beam!
What a devoted crew.
I've spotted him! Straw boy!
Right over there, Team Bay!
Huh?
Who's that?
And where is it coming from?
Huh?
Just as I suspected.
Didn't I tell you Luffy was going to be in trouble?
What the?
That face.
Why is it so gigantic?
I don't know.
I think it just does that.
Luffy!
Is he still alive?
Say something!
Oh, easy does it!
Ah!
Get off!
You are wasting our time!
Sorry.
I think this little fella belongs to you.
Eva!
Jin Bay!
Let me go!
Oh man!
Let go of my legs!
I'm so close to him!
Let go!
Enough!
He's done his fair share of good.
Treat him!
No!
Get off!
I don't have time for this!
Get away!
Let me go!
They're gonna...
I gotta...
Casey needs me!
Please!
He's my only brother!
I can't lose him!
I can't!
I'd rather die!
At any cost!
I gotta...
I promise...
I will...
I'll save him!
Aid him quick!
He's in bad shape.
Please, Sergeant.
Do everything within your power to help him.
I can't!
I'd rather die!
At any cost!
I gotta...
I promise!
I will...
I'll save him!
Nothing within your power to help him!
Luffy!
Can you hear me?
Stay with us, friend!
He's nothing but a big-mouthed kid who goes looking for trouble.
Dumb and clumsy.
Careless, too.
But I've got a soft spot for fools like him.
If you're ready to die, step up and meet your maker!
Oh, no!
Not again!
You...
You're always sailing around wreaking havoc.
But here...
You're through!
That's what you think!
I'll be right back!
You wait here!
Hold on!
You're leaving?
I must!
I won't rest until Ace is safe!
I'll be right back!
You wait here!
Hold on!
You're leaving?
I must!
I won't rest until Ace is safe!
Oh!
Stay away from me!
It's too late!
I'll be right back!
You wait here!
Hold on!
You're leaving?
I must!
I won't rest until Ace is safe!
Stay away from me!
It's too dangerous!
Die!
Damn you!
You...
shot it!
What a brittle sword!
Aah!!
Goddamn you!
Ah!
Halt!
Stay away from me!
Ah!
It's too dangerous!
Die!
Ha!
Damn you!
You...
shot it!
What a brittle sword!
Aah!
move it pops is coming through you think yourself brave but if you had any pride as swordsman
you'd know when to admit defeat
insolent wretches luffy i shall smite every man that stands between us i'm coming my love
she's attacking both sides moa hancock's completely lost it everyone cover your eyes quickly
slave arrows
lovely the corpse count's still on the rise
quit moving around you're mine
am i it sure feels like i'm roaming free
it's not over yet keep on the alert man
those are the new world pirates that were trapped in the bay
sorry for the wait nice about time just great we turned away for one second and this happens
uncle is not gonna like this we better clean up
so get ready show no mercy to our enemies and it's fine if a few soldiers get caught up in the crossfire
fire pacifistas
hang on ace i'm coming for you
he's flying what are you waiting for shoot him down
it's going straight through him never mind that just keep shooting
now this looks bad
yeah commander marco
marco's down
what's a big idea i never gave you orders to start fighting
we're doomed we have to fight monkey d garp
this can't be good
the legendary navy hero
we got this now they're finished he's the best gatekeeper there is
oh man
garp
if you want to reach the scaffold you're gonna have to make it through me first
stupid brats
faced with the might of the three admirals even whitebeard's most powerful fighters begin to falter
as ace watches his loved ones struggle in vain to save him he weeps questioning the meaning of his life
refusing to relent luffy begs ivanka for one last chance at victory
on the next one piece the power that will shorten one's life energy hormone redox
i'll find the winner
i'm gonna be king of the pirates
i'll be king of the pirates